Finding aid for the Connexxus/Centro de Mujeres collection, 1985-1991 LSC.1848
UCLA Library Special Collections
- Administrative Files, Series 2.; 3 boxes
  - Human Resources, 1985-1990; Subseries 1.; 22 folders
    - Employees, 1985-1989; 11 folders (Box 2, Folder 2 - 13)
      Restricted until January 2014.
  - Correspondence, 1985-1990; Subseries 2.; 12 folders
    Folders are arranged by alphabetically by type of correspondence.
    The correspondence has been divided into five categories - general, thank yous, letters of support, postcards and greeting cards, and political addresses. The "Political Addresses" folder contains mailing addresses, but not correspondence with political figures.
    - General, 1985-1991; 2 folders (Box 1, Folder 14 - 15)
      Includes correspondence to and from Yolanda Retter.
    - Thank Yous, 1985, 1988-1990; 8 folders (Box 1, Folder 19 - 26)
      Folder 19: Counseling Development Program Fund (1989)
      Folder 20: Five Plus Campaign (1989)
      Folder 21: Founders' Circle Pledges (1988-1989)
      Folder 22: General (1985, 1988-1990, mostly 1988-1989)
      Folder 23: June L. Mazer Collection (1989)
      Folder 24: Newsletter (1989)
      Folder 25: Services, Items, Time (1988-1989)
      Folder 26: United Way (1987-1989)
    - Letters of Support, 1989; 1 folder (Box 1, Folder 16)
      Includes letters of support for National Black Gay and Lesbian Conference, Project S.I.S.T.E.R. (Sexual Assault Crisis Services), Pasadena Rape Crisis Center
    - Postcards and Greeting Cards, 1985-1989; 1 folder (Box 1, Folder 18)
      Postcards and greeting cards received from Connexxus supporters. Also includes a "I [heart] Women" bumper sticker, 2 cartoons, and a flyer for Alcohol Abuse Program at GLCSC. Materials were used in a wall display at Connexxus (formerly in folder labeled "Postcards, wall display).
    - Political Addresses, n.d.; 1 folder (Box 1, Folder 17)
      Address list of members of Los Angeles City Council, Los Angeles Board of Supervisors, California Assembly and California Senate. Does not include actual correspondence with members.
  - Subject Files, 1982-1991; Subseries 3.; 53 folders
    Folders are arranged alphabetically by title. The majority of Connexxus' original file titles were retained; some have been altered to clarify the folder's contents.
    Contains materials generated by the administrative operations of Connexxus. Folders 31-33 contain extensive history on the founding of Connexxus.
    - "A", 1985-1988; 4 folders (Box 1, Folder 1 - 4)
      Folder 1: Activity Rosters (1986-1988)
      Folder 2: Advertisers List (1987)
      Folder 3: Artist in Residence: Terry Wolverton (1985-1986)
      Folder 4: ASL Interpreters (n.d.)
    - "B", 1984-1988; 3 folders (Box 1, Folder 5 - 7)
      Folder 5: Building Acquisition (1984-1988)
      Folder 6: Burglary (May 1988)
      Folder 7: Business Name (1984)
    - "C", 1982-1989; 4 folders (Box 1, Folder 8 - 11)
      Folder 8: California Self Help Center (n.d.)
      Folder 9: Certificates of Recognition (n.d.)
      Folder 10: Community Resources - Organizations (1984-1989)
      Folder 11: Community Resources - People (1982-1983)
      Folder 12: Contract Lending Agreements
      Folder 13: Contract for Services
    - "D", 1985-1986, 1988; 2 folders (Box 1, Folder 27 - 28)
      Folder 27: Data Sheets (1985-1986)
      Folder 28: Dispute Resolution Service (1988)
    - "F", 1983-1988; 5 folders (Box 1, Folder 29 - 33)
      Folder 29: Facility, 9504 Santa Monica Bl. (1984, 1986-1988)
      Folder 30: Facility Rental Form (n.d.)
      Folder 31: First Year Materials (1984-1985)
      Folder 32: Founding Herstory (1983-1985)
      Folder 33: Founding Papers (1984-1986)
      First Year Materials, Founding Herstory, and Founding Papers (Folders 31-33) contain extensive information on the founding of Connexxus - invitations, correspondence, bumper stickers, initial organizational meeting minutes, overview of committees and organizational structure, open letters to the community regarding the status of Connexxus, initial needs assessment survey, 1984 information sheet, correspondence with Southern California Women for Understanding and June Mazer, letter from Vanessa Romain regarding the portrayal of lesbians of color in an article about Connexxus published in the Lesbian News.
    - "G", 1984-1988; 3 folders (Box 1, Folder 34 - 36)
      Folder 34: Gay and Lesbian Community Services Center, GSLCSC (1988)
      Folder 35: Gay and Lesbian Task Force (1988)
      Folder 36: Guest Book (1984-1987)
    - "H", 1989; 1 folder (Box 1, Folder 60)
      Hyatt on Sunset (1989)
    - "I", 1990-1991; 4 folders (Box 1, Folder 46 - 49)
      Folder 46: Insurance (1990)
      Folder 47: Insurance: Liability and Package (1990-1991)
      Folder 48: Insurance: Liquor Liability (1990-1991)
      Folder 49: Internal Revenue Service (1990)
    - "L", 1988-1989, 1991; 4 folders (Box 1, Folder 50 - 53)
      Folder 50: Loan Agreement (n.d.)
      Folder 51: Legal Material (1991)
      Folder 52: Lesbian and Gay Public Awareness Project (1988-1989)
      Folder 53: Lesbian News (1991)
    - "N", 1989; 3 folders (Box 1, Folder 54 - 56)
      Folder 54: National Organization of Women / NOW (1989)
      Folder 55: Newsletter Ad Rates (n.d.)
      Folder 56: No on Proposition 64 (1986)
    - "P", 1980, 1989; 2 folders (Box 3, Folder 1 - 2)
      Folder 1: Permit - Plummer Park Facility (1989)
      Folder 2: Proof Report (1980)
    - "S", 1981, 1984-1990; 6 folders (Box 3, Folder 3 - 8)
      Folder 3: San Diego Lesbian News (1988)
      Folder 4: Signs (n.d.)
      Folder 5: Southern California Women for Understanding / SCWU (1981, 1985)
      Folder 6: Southern California Women for Understanding / SCWU: Monthly Reports (1984-1985)
      Folder 7: Social Service Report Forms / Permits (1984-1990)
      Folder 8: Social Service Solicitation (1988-1990)
      San Diego Lesbian News (Folder 73) contains copy of Together, UCLA's lesbian feminist magazine.
    - "T", 1987-1988; 1 folder (Box 3, Folder 9)
      Tax Board (1987-1988)
    - "U", 1988-1989; 2 folders (Box 3, Folder 10 - 11)
      Folder 10: UCLA Workstudy (1988-1989)
      Folder 11: User Information Form (n.d.)
    - "V", 1984-1989 (Box 3, Folder 12 - 20)
      Folder 12: Video (You Can Know All I Am) - General (1988-1989)
      Folder 13: Video - Correspondence (1988)
      Folder 14: Video - Lending Contract (1989)
      Folder 15: Video - Orders (1989)
      Folder 16: Video - Production (1985-1988)
      Folder 17: Video - Screening (1988)
      Folder 18: Video - Signed Releases (1988)
      Folder 19: Volunteers (1984-1988)
      Folder 20: Volunteer Recognition (n.d.)
- Events, 1984-1989; Series 3.; 2 boxes, 1.5 linear feet
  This Events series comprises of documentation related to the planning, publicity, and execution of Connexxus' various social events, workshops, and conferences. The majority of the folders within this series are labeled according to event. Folders 54-57 contain photographs from select events.
  - Ad Books, 1984-1988; 1 folder (Box 6, Folder 1)
    Contains letter of solicitation for advertisements as well as books of advertisements from events such as Casino Cabaret (1984-1985), Founding Celebration (1987-1988), and Follies (1985?).
    Contained photocopies of personal checks from donors for "Gay Men's Ad" in 1988. These were shredded in January 2008.
  - Dance Cards, 1988-1989; 1 folder (Box 6, Folder 8)
    Includes dance card order forms, dance card order procedures, handwritten correspondence from donors, list of donors.
  - Events, 1984-1989; 28 folders (Box 6 - 7, Folder 2 - 53, 58)
    Includes flyers, programs, event paperwork, correspondence, planning documentation, and list of attendees.
    Box 6
    Folder 2: All Around Time (1988)
    Folder 3: Auction (1986)
    Folder 4: Casino Cabaret (1984)
    Folder 5: Casino Cabaret (1985)
    Folder 6: Conference, Lesbian Mothers (1987)
    Folder 7: Conference, Old Lesbians (1988)
    Folder 9: Dances (1987)
    Folder 10: Dances (1988)
    Folder 11: Dances (1989)
    Folder 12: A Day at the Races (1988)
    Folder 13: Dinah Shore Picnic (1988)
    Folder 14: Eisenberg, Mary Jane Dance Company Benefit (1988)
    Folder 15: Family Dinner (1988)
    Folder 17: Follies (1985)
    Folder 19: Founders Dinner (1986)
    Folder 20-21: Founders Dinner (1987)
    Folder 22-25: Founders Dinner (1988)
    Folder 26: Founders Dinner (1989)
    Folder 27: Gay Pride Festival (1986)
    Folder 28: Hoedown (1989)
    Folder 29: Hollywood Bowl (1987)
    Folder 30-31: Lily's
    Folder 32: Multicultural Festival (1988)
    Folder 33: Multicultural Festival (1989)
    Box 7
    Folder 24: National March for Women's Lives
    Folder 1: Open House (1988)
    Folder 2 Sarton, May (1988)
    Folder 3: Starscene Festival (1987)
    Folder 4: Summer Soiree (1986)
    Folder 5: Sunset Junction Festival (1987-1989)
    Folder 6: Lily Tomlin and Jane Wagner (1987)
    Folder 7: Walk/Run (1985)
    Folder 8: West Hollywood Street Festival (n.d.)
    Folder 9: Women's Winter Gala (1984)
    Folder 10: Workshop - Bunche, Charlotte (1989)
    Folder 11: Workshop on The Body - Coffey, Susa (1989)
    Folder 12: Workshop - General (1988)
    Folder 13: Workshop on Lesbian Ethics - Hoaglund, Sara Lucia (1989)
    Folder 14: Workshop - Lesbian Battering (1988)
    Folder 15: Workshop - Math (1989)
    Folder 16: Workshop - Ramos, Laura J. (n.d.)
    Folder 17: Workshop on building productive work and personal relationships - Reap What You Sow (n.d.)
    Folder 18: Workshop - Spirituality (1988)
    Folder 19: Workshop - Vad Den Bergh, Nan (n.d.)
  - Flyers, 1984-1990; 1 folder (Box 6, Folder 16)
    Contains flyers from various Connexxus events.
  - Forms, n.d.; 1 folder (Box 6, Folder 18)
    Contains blank forms tracking ticket sales, event planning, event budget, spreadsheet of events and expenses, food tickets, door prize entries, event item checklist, and profitability summary.
  - Photographs, 1984-1987; 4 folders (Box 7, Folder 20 - 23)
    Folder 20: Follies (1985), contains 22 color and black and white photo prints, subjects are unidentified, photographer unknown
    Folder 21: Founders Celebration (1984), contains thirty-five black and white photo prints and five contact sheets, subjects are unidentified, photographer Mary Whitlock
    Folder 22: Summer Soiree (1986), contains eight color photo prints, subjects unidentified, photographer unknown
    Folder 23: Various Events (ca. 1986-1987), contains fifty-two color and black and white photo prints and two contact sheets, includes photography by Mary Whitlock and photos of the first Connexxus office, Bunny McCulloch, Del Martinez, Lauren Jardine, Pat Martel, Carol Anderson, Lee Werbel, Jeanne Cordova, Dina Bachelor, Art Hagopian, Phil Sheley, and John Olson
  - Workshop Forms, n.d.; 1 folder (Box 6, Folder 34)
    Contains blank forms for workshop sign ups, attendance confirmation, training evaluations, services rendered receipt.
- Financial Records, 1985-1991; Series 4.; 3 boxes, 2.5 linear feet
  The Financial Records series contain materials related to accounting, Connexxus' various bank accounts, financial statements and general ledger, loans, manual of financial procedures, taxes, and funding from the City of West Hollywood.
  - Accountants, 1988-1990; 1 folder (Box 12, Folder 1)
  - Accounting, 1987-1990; 1 folder (Box 12, Folder 2)
  - Audit, 1989-1990; 1 folder (Box 12, Folder 3)
  - Bad Checks, 1989; 1 folder (Box 12, Folder 4)
    Photocopies of checks from personal donors' bank accounts were removed and shredded in 2008.
  - Bank Statements, 1986-1991; 5 folders (Box 12, Folder 5 - 9)
    Folder 5: All Accounts (1986-1988, 1991)
    Folder 6: Money Market Account (1988-1989)
    Folder 7: Operating Account (1988-1989)
    Folder 8: Sanwa Account (1988-1989)
    Folder 9: West Hollywood Account (1988-1989)
  - Bank of Los Angeles - Alliance Account, 1987-1989; 1 folder (Box 12, Folder 10)
  - Budget, 1990; 1 folder (Box 12, Folder 11)
  - Cancelled Checks, 1990-1991; 4 folders (Box 12, Folder 12 - 15)
    Folder 12: All Accounts (1990-1991)
    Folder 13: West Hollywood Account (1988-1989)
    Folder 14: General Account - Bank of Los Angeles (1988-1989)
    Folder 15: General Account - Sanwa Bank (1988-1989)
  - Chart of Accounts, 1986, 1988; 1 folder (Box 12, Folder 16)
  - Checks, 1 folder; 1990-1991 (Box 12, Folder 17)
  - Checks (Carbons), 1988-1991; 7 folders (Box 12, Folder 18 - 24)
    Folder 18: Alliance Account (1990-1991)
    Folder 19: General Account (1988)
    Folder 20: General Account (1989)
    Folder 21: General Account (1990-1991)
    Folder 22: Mazer Account (1990-1991)
    Folder 23: West Hollywood Account (1988-1989)
    Folder 24: West Hollywood Account (1990)
  - Check Registers, 1987-1990; 2 folders (Box 12, Folder 25 - 26)
    Folder 25: All Accounts - Books (1988-1990)
    Folder 26: All Accounts - Printouts (1987-1988)
  - Checks to Be Written, 1988-1990; 1 folder (Box 12, Folder 27)
  - Deposits, 1986-1988; 2 folders (Box 12, Folder 28 - 29)
    See Note field for items marked with an asterisk.
    Folder 28: Operating Fund (1986-1988)
    Folder 29: February 1988*
    Photocopied checks from donors' personal accounts were removed and shredded in January 2008.
  - Deposits, 1988-1991; 13 folders (Box 13, Folder 1 - 13)
    See Note field for entries marked with an asterisk.
    Folder 1: March 1988*
    Folder 2: July 1988*
    Folder 3: August 1988*
    Folder 4: September 1988*
    Folder 5: October 1988*
    Folder 6: November 1988*
    Folder 7: December 1988*
    Folder 8: January 1989*
    Folder 9: February 1989*
    Folder 10: March 1989*
    Folder 11: April 1989*
    Folder 12: June 1989*
    Folder 13: All Accounts (August 1990 - February 1991)
    Photocopies of checks from donors' personal accounts were removed and shredded in January 2008.
  - Financial Statement and Ledger, 1985-1991; 15 folders (Box 13, Folder 14 - 27, 32, 40)
    Folder 14: 30 November 1985
    Folder 15: 1985-1987
    Folder 32: July 1988
    Folder 16: August 1988
    Folder 17: September 1988
    Folder 18: October 1988
    Folder 19: November 1988
    Folder 20: December 1988
    Folder 21: January 1989
    Folder 22: February 1989
    Folder 23: March 1989
    Folder 24: April 1989
    Folder 25: May 1989
    Folder 26: June 1989
    Folder 27: July 1990 - April 1991 Folder 40: May 1990
  - Loans, 1985-1989; 1 folder (Box 13, Folder 28)
    Photocopies of checks from personal accounts were removed and shredded in January 2008.
  - Log of Pledges, Donations, and Deposits, 1985; 1 folder (Box 13, Folder 29)
  - Merchant Banking, 1989; 1 folder (Box 13, Folder 30)
  - Procedures Manual, n.d.; 1 folder (Box 13, Folder 31)
    See also "Board: Financial Procedures Manual."
  - Receipt Book, 1988; 4 folders (Box 13, Folder 33 - 36)
    Folder 33: 1988
    Folder 34: 1 February 1989 - 14 April 1989
    Folder 35: 18 April 1989 - 1 June 1989
    Folder 36: Workshops (3 February 1989)
  - Miscellaneous Financial Records, 1980, 1991; 1 folder (Box 13, Folder 37)
    Includes IRS correspondence, bank statements, receipts, assumption of liabilities documents, handwritten to-do list of tasks for Connexxus' closing,
  - Financial Reports, 1986-1991; 2 folders (Box 13, Folder 38 - 39)
    Folder 38: 1990-1991
    Folder 39: 1986
  - Taxes, 1985-1990; 1 folder (Box 13, Folder 41)
  - Tax Returns, 1989; 1 folder (Box 13, Folder 42)
  - West Hollywood, 1989-1990; 2 folders (Box 13, Folder 43 - 44)
    Folder 43: Funding (1989-1990)
    Folder 44: West Hollywood Budget (1989-1990)
  - West Hollywood, 1989-1990; 12 folders (Box 14, Folder 1 - 12)
    Folder 1: Cash Disbursements (1987-1988)
    Folder 2: City Council (1988)
    Folder 3: Contract (1985-1986)
    Folder 4: Correspondence (1985-1989)
    Folder 5: Forms (1989-1990)
    Folder 6: Grant Monthly Reports (1985-1987)
    Folder 7: Program Services Reports (1989)
    Folder 8: Publicity Material (n.d.)
    Folder 9: 1986-1987
    Folder 10: 1988-1989
    Folder 11: 1989-1990
    Folder 12: Closeout (July 1990)
- Fundraising, 1985-1990; Series 5.; 2 boxes
  Contains materials related to Connexxus' fundraising campaigns and donations.
  - Fundraising Campaigns, 1985-1989; 9 folders (Box 15, Folder 1 - 9)
    For entries marked with an *, see the Note field.
    Folder 1: Board Friend Campaign (1987)
    Folder 2: Brothers for Sisters - General (1986-1987)*
    Folder 3: Brothers for Sisters - Pledges (1986-1987)
    Folder 4: Colin Higgins Foundation (1989)
    Folder 5: Direct Mail Piece (1985)
    Folder 6: Donations (1985-1986)
    Folder 7: Donations (1987)
    Folder 8: Five Plus Connexxus Campaign (1988)
    Folder 9: Founding Circle Members (1980-1987)
    Photocopies of checks from donor's personal accounts were shredded in January 2008.
  - Fundraising Campaigns, 1985-1990; 13 folders (Box 16, Folder 1 - 14)
    Folder 1: Fundraising General Info (1985-1988)
    Folder 2: Get Connected Fund (1986)
    Folder 3: Holiday Campaign Phone Script and Forms (n.d.)
    Folder 4: Holiday Campaign (1986)
    Folder 5: Holiday Campaign (1988)
    Folder 6: Holiday Campaign (1989)
    Folder 7: Home Parties (1989)
    Folder 8: Honolulu Raffle (1987)
    Folder 9: Mexico Relief Donations (1985)*
    Folder 10: Pledges (1986-1988)
    Folder 11: Pledge Reminder Letters (n.d.)
    Folder 12: Siegel, Sharon (1985-1988)
    Folder 13: Solicitation Letter (n.d.)
    Folder 14: United Way (1989-1990)
- Programs, 1984-1990; Series 6.; 2 boxes, 1.5 linear feet
  Contains materials related to Connexxus committees and programs - Connexxus East, Connexxus Business and Professional Women's Alliance (CBPWA) / The Alliance, Economic Empowerment, June L. Mazer Collection, mental health, rap groups, and referrals. The series also includes completed surveys distributed by Connexxus to assess their services.
  - Community Services Survey, n.d.; 1 folder (Box 8, Folder 1)
    Contains blank community survey, completed community services, and tally of results
  - Centro de Mujeres / Connexxus East, 1986-1990; 4 folders (Box 8, Folder 2 - 4, 21)
    Folder 2: General (1986-1990) - Includes information on the opening of Connexxus East as well as the effects of Connexxus' closing, correspondence from Yolanda Retter
    Folder 3: Outreach (1986-1987)
    Folder 21: Latina Lesbian Mental Health Conference (1986-1987) - Includes 21 black and white photo prints, subjects and photographer unidentified
    Folder 4: Projects (1986-1987) - Contains black and white photo contact sheet of portraits of Guadalupe Juarez taken by Laura Aguilar
  - Connexxus Business and Professional Women's Alliance (CBPWA) / The Alliance, 1990; 7 folders (Box 8, Folder 5 - 11)
    Folder 5: Financial (1990)
    Folder 6: Forms (n.d.)
    Folder 7: Membership Directory (1987-1988)
    Folder 8: Membership Materials (1987-1988)
    Folder 9: Minutes (1985-1986)
    Folder 10: Publicity (n.d.)
    Folder 11: Special Events (1987-1989)
  - Committees, 1986-1987; 5 folders (Box 8, Folder 12 - 16)
    Folder 12: Latina Advisory (1986-1987)
    Folder 13: Lesbians in Battering Relationships Resources (1987-1988, 1990)
    Folder 14: General (1984-1985) - Contains minutes, list of committee members, and miscellaneous documents by the Counseling, Programs, and Needs Assessment committees
    Folder 15: Mental Health (1987)
    Folder 16: Women's Issues (1989-1990)
  - Economic Empowerment, 1985-1989; 4 folders (Box 8, Folder 17 - 20)
    Folder 17: General (1985-1986)
    Folder 18: Bunches of Balloons (1986-1989)
    Folder 19: State Board of Equalization (1986)
    Folder 20: Lesbian Greeting Card Project (1986-1987) - Includes artwork by Mar Gorman, Miki Jackson and Laura Aguilar
  - June L. Mazer Collection, 1984-1990; 9 folders (Box 8, Folder 22 - 30)
    Folder 22: Correspondence (1987-1990)
    Folder 23: Bunny MacCulloch Trust (1988-1990)
    Folder 24: Chicago Resource Center, Grant Application (1987)
    Folder 25: Contract (1988-1990)
    Folder 26: Donations (1987)
    Folder 27: Grants (1989)
    Folder 28: Mazer Biography (1987)
    Folder 29: Miscellaneous (1987-1990) - Contains press and notes
    Folder 30: West Coast Lesbian Collection (1984-1986)
  - Mental Health, 1985-1990; 12 folders (Box 8 - 9, Folder 31 - 42)
    Box 8
    Folder 31: Correspondence (1985-1990)
    Folder 32: Courage to Heal Workshop (1989) - Includes press photos of Laura Davis
    Folder 33: Courage to Heal Workshop Evaluations (1989)
    Folder 34: Ethics and Professional Standards Subcommittee (1985-1986)
    Folder 35: Incest Survival (1988-1989)
    Box 9
    Folder 1: Intern Applications (1986)
    Folder 2: Guidelines (n.d.)
    Folder 3: Sign In Sheets (1990)
    Folder 4: Therapists (1985)
    Folder 5: Therapist Referral Letter (n.d.)
    Folder 6: Therapist Workshops (1988)
    Folder 7: Therapist Workshop Series (1989)
  - Rap Groups, 1984-1989; 5 folders (Box 9, Folder 43 - 47)
    Folder 8: Facilitators (1988-1989)
    Folder 9: Facilitators' Guidelines (n.d.)
    Folder 10: Lists (1984-1988)
    Folder 11: Training (1989)
    Folder 12: Topics (1987)
  - Referrals, 1989; 1 folder (Box 9, Folder 13)
- Publicity and Publications, 1984-1990; Series 7.; 2 boxes, 1.5 linear feet
  The Newsletter subseries contains newsletters produced by Connexxus and its programs. It also includes press releases, press clippings, publicity ephemera, and promotional photos. The Publicity Binders provide a chronological, comprehensive view of Connexxus news and events.
  Folders are arranged alphabetically by title and chronologically when appropriate.
  - Advertisements, 1984-1988; 1 folder (Box 10, Folder 55)
    Contains bumper stickers, buttons (made by Yolanda Retter), early press releases, received solicitations for advertising, event listings, and advertisements in event programs.
  - Fact Sheets, n.d.; 1 folder (Box 10, Folder 60)
  - Five Plus Connexxus Campaign, 1988; 1 folder (Box 10, Folder 56)
    Contains Connexxus newsletter (March 1988), mailing envelope, bumper sticker, lapel pins, letter, flyers, and newspaper inserts produced by the Five Plus Connexxus Campaign
  - Press Clippings, 1984-1989; 2 folders (Box 10, Folder 57-58)
    Includes clippings from publications such as Frontiers, The Lesbian News, L.A. Weekly, Les Meet: The Lesbian Entertainment Magazine, The News, The SCWU Newsletter, Ten Percent: UCLA Lesbian and Gay Newsmagazine, and The Post.
  - Press Releases, 1985-1988; 6 folders (Box 10, Folder 49 - 54)
    Folder 49: 1985
    Folder 50: 1986
    Folder 51: 1987
    Folder 52: 1988
    Folder 53: No date
    Folder 54: Press Lists
  - Publicity Binders, 1985-1990; 2 bound volumes (Box 11)
    Volume 1 (black cover) contains newsletters, job announcements, and flyers bound together chronologically from February 1985 through December 1987.
    Volume 2 (maroon cover) begins at January 1988 and continues through June 1990.
  - Promotional Photographs, 1988; 1 folder (Box 10, Folder 59)
    Contains four 8x10 black and white photo prints of Connexxus staff (Gini Morton, Maureen McTeague / Moe, Mary Galloway, Denise Wheeler / Executive Director, Cheryl Mendoza, Wendy Goodfriend, Margaret Smith) taken by Laura Aguilar. Photos are presumably for the Five Plus Connexxus campaign. One photo includes the text "Tis the season's [sic] to be giving remember 5+ or this will be our new home."
  - Newsletters, 1985-1990; Subseries 1.; 48 folders
    Folders are arranged alphabetically by newsletter title and chronologically within each newsletter run.